Tufts CEM Report UP074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts CEM Report
1985 -- 1994
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Center for Environmental Management
UP074
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains quarterly reports of the Center for Environmental Management between 1985 and 1994. It is published by the Center for Environmental Management, a division of the department of Urban and Environmental Policy.
Biographical / Historical
Developed by Jean Mayer in 1984, the Center for Environmental Management is an independent center concerned with the problems of hazardous and solid wastes and toxic substances.
- Tufts CEM Report, 1985 -- 1994; UP074.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains quarterly reports of the Center for Environmental Management between 1985 and 1994. It is published by the Center for Environmental Management, a division of the department of Urban and Environmental Policy.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically and then as found.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts CEM Report, Spring, 1986; UP074.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Center for Environmental Management.
  - Tufts CEM Report, Fall, 1986; UP074.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Winter, 1986; UP074.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Summer, 1987; UP074.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Spring, 1989; UP074.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Summer, 1990; UP074.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Spring, 1991; UP074.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Spring, 1994; UP074.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Winter, 1989; UP074.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Fall, 1986; UP074.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Summer, 1986; UP074.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Summer, 1985; UP074.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tufts CEM Report, Spring, 1986; UP074.001.001.00013 (Box 1)